Y-You want to have...
sex for five whole days?!
Yes!
What better way to make use of
your five days of paid vacation?
But what about stuff
like my needing to eat?!
We wouldn't be doing it
for the entire five-day period.
For instance, we'd start with...
Hugging...
And simply holding hands.
We'd spend four days entirely on foreplay
before saving the main event for the very end!
I think that would make
for a lovely vacation!
Ah, I see~
Nadeshiko, would you... be
happy if I could do that?
Oh, yes, of course!
All right, then. Let's give it a try.
Okay!
DAY
We start with a day of
slowly sharing our affections!
She wall-slammed me?!
Nobody's...  ever wall-slammed me before...
it's kinda...
It's kinda cute...
DAY
This is different than when
we usually kiss with tongue...
Is kissing all we're doing today?
Yes.
I wasn't quite sure
what to expect at first...
but going slow like this isn't half bad.
DAY
N-Nadeshiko!
You said we were saving
this for the very end!
Well, for today touching
below the belt is off-limits
so I'm helping myself to
your upper body instead!
Nadeshiko! C'monnnn..!
All right! That's enough for today!
We're saving climax for
the last day, remember?
Huh? But...
I'm too horny to fall asleep!
DAY
Shall we focus our attentions
below the belt today?
Huh?!
For instance...
the groin...
Or rubbing your lower abdomen...
Pressing in teasingly with my fingers...
I knew it. Another day where she's
just going to work me up...!
If it feels this good now,
what in the world is
tomorrow gonna be like?!
DAY
Final Day
Now then...
Are you ready for us to begin, Akane?
I've been so unfulfilled
I can't even sleep!
All right.
If I may, then.
All that from just one finger?!
Um, Akane?
Sorry for making you hold out so long,
but I need you to hold still
for just a little bit longer, okay?
Huh?!
Right now, the slightest stimulation
can cause incredible pleasure, so...
Let's take time for you
to get used to it, all right?
- Nadeshiko...
- Yes?
- Nadeshiko!
- It'll be all right.
Nadeshiko...
I just want you to feel as
good as possible, okay?
Hey, Akane...
You don't have to keep
holding back anymore.
Feel free to tell me
what you'd like me to do.
M-More...
I just need more!
Okay.
I am working from home tomorrow...
Oh, I'm so sorry! Did I overdo it?
Regardless, I'm so happy right now.
It's like I've finally
fulfilled my purpose...
Nadeshiko...
Yeah! Like a washing
machine, or a microwave!
Uhh...
Nadeshiko... sure does say very "robot"
things from time to time.
I mean, she sure does seem fond of me,
but is that just because of
her romance-bot programming?
I love that...
I'm going to keep getting
to hear you call me by my name.
Every time I hear you say "Nadeshiko,"
it makes me feel so good inside.
I'm so glad I got to hear
it so many t times today!
Sure thing.
I guess...
I don't need to overthink things for now.
Thanks for watching!
Brought to you by ToonsHub